听力材料：一、听力技能。
对话理解。
根据你所听到的对话，从
,B Hello, Tom.
三个选项中。
选择最佳选项，回答问题。
听下面五段对话，每听完一段对话，回答一个小题。
一。
Where are and Lucy?
They are in the classroom now.
Lily is reading and Lucy is writing.
Question Who is reading?
Two What bad weather these days.
I miss the sunny days.
Me too. It's raining heavily, but we can have a water fight.
Question What is the weather like?
What bad weather these days.
I miss the sunny days.
Me too. It's raining heavily, but we can have a water fight.
Question What is the weather like?
Three How did you come to school yesterday, Billy?
took a bus to school yesterday, but I usually come to school by bike.
Question How did Billy come to school yesterday?
How did you come to school yesterday, Billy?
took a bus to school yesterday, but I usually come to school by bike.
Question How did Billy come to school yesterday?
Four Mary, what's your favorite food, fried rice, pizza or sushi?
Mary, prefer fried rice to sushi.
However, I like pizza best.
Question How did to yesterday, What does Mary like best?
Mary, what's your favorite food, fried rice, pizza or sushi?
I prefer fried rice to sushi.
However, I like pizza best.
Question What does Mary like best?
Five Mr. Scott will give a speech about classroom teaching next Friday.
Oh, what a pity!
I'll have to be at a meeting that day.
Question What will the woman have to do next Friday?
Mr. Scott will give a speech about classroom teaching next Friday.
Oh, what a pity!
I'll have to be at a meeting that day.
Question What will the woman have to do next Friday?
听第六段对话，回答六至七小题。
What will next Friday?
Shall we go to fly kites tomorrow?
Sorry, I can't make it.
I'm going to have a picnic with my family.
That's wonderful. Do you have a picnic every month?
Yes, my mom will make some French food for us this time.
We all like it.
That sounds fun.
Would you like to go with us?
My uncle will drive us there.
Yes, I'd love to.
Shall we go to fly kites tomorrow?
Sorry, I can't make it.
I'm going to have a picnic with my family.
That's wonderful. Do you have a picnic every month?
Yes, my mom will make some French food for us this time.
We all like it.
That sounds fun.
Would you like to go with us?
My uncle will drive us there.
Yes, I'd love to.
Question 6 What will the boy do tomorrow?
Question 7 How often does the boy have a picnic?
Question You look nice in red.
听第七段对话，回答八至九小题。
Thank you, Mr.
Green. It's my favorite color.
My wife likes red, too.
But my daughter likes white.
I know she has many white t -shirts.
Oh, I haven't seen her for a long time.
Where has she gone?
She has gone to Paris on business.
She has been there for two months.
You look nice in red.
Thank you, Mr.
Green. It's my favorite color.
My wife likes red, too.
But my daughter likes white.
I know she has many white t -shirts.
Oh, I haven't seen her for a long time.
Where has she gone?
She has gone to Paris on business.
She has been there for two months.
Question 8 What color does Mr.
Green's daughter like?
Question 9 Where is Mr.
Green's daughter now?
听第八段对话，回答。
十至十二小题。
Very few people come to this coffee house at this time.
I'm a dance teacher.
I just rest for about 30 minutes here and then go to have a class in my dance school
at 3. Wow!
Your job is cool.
Thank you. Why are you here?
I spend most of my time in my office.
And I like to meet people here.
I feel more relaxed here than in the office.
I see. Oh, here comes a young lady.
She is the person I just want to meet.
Hello, madam. Can I sit here?
Of course. Very few people come to this coffee house at this time.
I'm a dance teacher.
I just rest for about 30 minutes here and then go to have a class in my dance school
at 3. Wow!
Your job is cool.
Thank you. Why are you here?
I spend most of my time in my office.
And I like to people here.
I feel more relaxed here than in the office.
I see. Oh, here comes a young lady.
She is the person I just want to meet.
Question 10 Where are the speakers?
Question 11 How made the woman feel now?
Question 12 Who does the woman want to meet here?
听第九段对话。
回答十三至十五小题。
Mr. Brown, I can't find my little brother.
When and where did you find him missing?
Just several minutes ago.
There was a girl singing songs in the street.
I just listened to her for a while and then I found he was lost.
What shall I do?
Don't worry. Let me know your brother's name, age, height, and the color of his
hair. His name is Jack, 5 years old.
He is a head shorter than me, about 120 centimeters tall.
And his hair is brown.
And his eyes are black.
Mr. Brown, I can't find my little brother.
When and where did you find him missing?
Just several minutes ago.
There was a girl singing songs in the street.
I just listened to her for a while and then I found he was lost.
What shall I Don't worry.
Let me know your brother's name, age, height, and the color of his hair.
His name is Jack, 5 years old.
He is a head shorter than me, about 120 centimeters tall.
And his hair is brown.
And his eyes are black.
Um, what clothes is he wearing?
He is wearing brown pants and a yellow hat.
Okay, we'll do our best to find him.
Question 13. What was Jane doing when she found her brother was lost?
was Jane doing when she found her brother was lost?
Question 14. How old is Jane's brother?
How old is Jane's brother?
Question 15. What is the man most probably?
What is the man most probably?
Question